

# JONATHAN HANSEN

Apache Junction, AZ 85120

Kriah0872@gmail.com

4803136648

Current enrolled in the U of A coding bootcamp and am seeking a job in the web development/software development industry. Contact me if you want to collaborate on any projects as I am eager to expand my knowledge and experience in the field. 3 years experience in the design/graphics industry. Have a taste for high functionality with a minimalist aesthetic. Authorized to work in the US for any employer

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### **Employee**

Decal Monkey LLC - Gilbert, AZ November 2019 to Present Cut Vinyl Layer Decals Install Decals Take orders from customers

#### **Production Worker**

Five18 Designs

May 2017 to October 2019

Over the years I had several job responsibilities, starting as a general laborer, advancing to operating latex vinyl printers, laminators and cutters (HP 365 Printer, Onyx RIP Software, Roland VS 540i, Graphtec FC 8600, Seal 54" Cold Laminator)

Applying vinyl decals, measuring ensuring decals are straight and centered

Applying heat transfer decals to garments

Short experience operating a manual silk screen T-shirt press

Prepping/ disassembling vehicles for installation

Creating invoices for customers

In charge of purchasing 500+ t shirt orders and scheduling jobs for wraps and t shirt jobs

Customer service/sales informing customers on our processes and selling the wraps/ t shirts

## **Universal Agent**

### **Affinitas Corporation**

November 2016 to March 2017

Customer support rep/ Quality Assurance Agent Customer support rep/ Quality Assurance Agent

### **Line Cook**

#### **IHOP**

February 2016 to November 2016

Prepare all food, prep, dishes, bussing, trash.

## **EDUCATION**

## None in Full Stack Web Development

**UofA** - Gilbert, AZ February 2020 to Present

# **General Education Diploma**

Mesa Community College - Mesa, AZ

October 2019

## **SKILLS**

- Customer Service (2 years)
- Printing (1 year)
- Customer service
- Invoices (2 years)
- Buying (1 year)
- Buying/procurement
- Procurement
- Quality assurance (2 years)
- Food service
- General labor (5 years)
- Excel
- Ms word
- Word
- Illustrator (Less than 1 year)
- Adobe illustrator

# **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION**

Dedicated, hardworking individual. Used to working in a fast-paced, high-pressure environments.

Very tech savvy (skilled in MS Word, Excel, some experience with Adobe Illustrator)

Skilled in customer service, face to face and over the phone experience.